alltheinternet.com 2004-06-03

# All the Internet - Our Privacy Statement

All the Internet Privacy Statement

All the Internet takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**Privacy Policy**  
All the Internet respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use All the Internet's search engine. Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Statement").

**All the Internet and Cookies**  
Upon your first visit to All the Internet, All the Internet sends a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. All the Internet uses cookies to improve the quality of our search engine. All the Internet does this by storing user preferences in cookies. All the Internet will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of All the Internet may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
All the Internet **does not** collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. All the Internet notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users.

**Links to Other Sites**  
The sites displayed as search results or linked to by All the Internet are developed by people over whom All the Internet exercises no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. All the Internet may choose to exhibit its search results in the form of a "URL redirecter." When All the Internet uses a URL redirecter, if you click on a URL from a search result, information about the click is sent to All the Internet, and All the Internet in turn sends you to the site you clicked on. All the Internet uses this URL information to understand and improve the quality of All the Internet's search. For instance, All the Internet uses this information to determine how often users are satisfied with the first result of a query and how often they proceed to later results.

**With Whom Does All the Internet Share Information?**  
All the Internet may share information about you with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information about our users and will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent. For example, we may disclose how frequently the average All the Internet user visits All the Internet, or which other query words are most often used with the query word "Windows." Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

**Is All the Internet Spyware or Malware?**  
All the Internet does not monitor, collect data or 'spy' on its user base. Any software program that is implying or reporting that All the Internet is 'spyware' or 'malware' is incorrect. All the Internet is incapable of tracking your overall web use or deciphering anything on your hard drive.

**Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy**  
By using the All the Internet web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy. All the Internet may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Questions and Suggestions**  
If you have questions or suggestions, please [Contact Us](http://www.alltheinternet.com/texis/open/allthru?ss=a&area=feedback) or you can mail us at: 

All the Internet  
Privacy Policies  
350 South Center Street  
Suite 500  
Reno, NV 89501  
(775) 333-5979
